Hanks, Paul; Papers apap253
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1961-1965; Undated; 2; 1.3 cubic ft.
  - I. 3879, P. 3994, An Act to Amend the Code of Criminal Procedure, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - I. 3964, P. 4164, An Act to Amend the Public Authorities Law, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - I. 3979, P. 4094, An Act to Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - I. 4022, P. 4224, An Act to Amend the Civil Service Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - I. 4126, P. 4278, An Act in Relation to the Apportionment of Public Moneys, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - I. 4165, P. 4399, An Act to Amend the Executive Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - I. 4227, P. 4491, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - I. 4331, P. 4596, An Act Authorizing the City of Rochester to Discontinue the Use of Certain Lands, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - I. 4332, P. 4597, An Act to Authorize the City of Monroe to Make a Portion of Mt. Read Blvd., A County Road, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - I. 4372, P. 4547, An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, 1963; 1965 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - I. 4475, P. 4661, An Act to Amend the Labor Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - I. 4499, P. 5391, An Act to Amend the County Law (For Release in the Afternoon Papers), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - I. 4869, P. 5167, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - I.S. 2606, I.S. 4220, P.S. 2746, P.A. 4383, An Act to Amend the Public Authorities Law, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - In Assembly Transcript, 65th Day of the 186 Session, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Introduction of Bills, Undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Legislative Committee on Docks, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Memorandum in Opposition of Amending Section 88, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Memorandum in Opposition to: An Act to Amend Public Land Law, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Memorandum in Support of A. Pr. 19, A. Int. No. 19, Undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Memorandum in Support of Bill to Amend the Military Law, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Memorandum on Social Legislation, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Memorandum on Social Legislation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Memorandum Re: An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Memorandum Urging Amendment to the NYC General Business and Financial Tax Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Message to the Legislature, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Union, Undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Notice for the Purpose of Substitution by Hanks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Office of Legislative Research (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Office of Legislative Research (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Onondaga County Legislation, Onondaga County New York, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Passed Bills, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Power Authority of the State of New York, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Program of Suggested State Legislation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Public Defender Bill (Representation of Indigent Persons), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Raccoon Bill, Undated; 1964 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Regulations Affecting Chauffeur Licenses, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Report of the Joint Legislation Committee on the Barge Canal, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Report of the Joint Legislation Committee on Winter Tourist Business, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Law Revision Commission for 1964, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Report to the New York State legislature, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Senate Bills: Military Affairs, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Psychopath Laws of the United States, 1962; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Spaying Legislation, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Statement to the Joint Legislative Hearing on the Budget-Albany, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Temporary Commission on Revision of the Penal Law and Criminal Code, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - To the Members of the New York State Legislature, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)